<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ismaël&#39;s blog on </title>
    <link>https://ismaelsow.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ismaël&#39;s blog on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ismaelsow.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Notion Paradox: When People Love &#34;Bloated&#34; Products</title>
      <link>https://ismaelsow.com/the-notion-paradox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ismaelsow.com/the-notion-paradox/</guid>
      <description>Notion is a spectacular success story, a textbook rocket ship. Between 2019 and 2020 alone, its number of users grew from one million to over four million. When the pandemic filled the startup world with a freezing terror, Notion raised $50 million in 36 hours. A deluge of fabulous reviews keeps pouring. Passioned tweets, exalted Youtube videos, grassroots meetups. That&amp;rsquo;s the stuff of dreams, for countless entrepreneurs, product managers, and designers from San Francisco to Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>❤️ I Love UXR.</title>
      <link>https://ismaelsow.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ismaelsow.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Ismaël. I write user research software and articles about&amp;hellip; user research. I used to be a software developer, an analytics consultant, and an A/B testing fanatic. I worked at Yahoo! and did consulting for several French enterprise companies like Carrefour and Orange.
I had a lot of dreams when I was young. The dinosaurs have disappeared since. 🦖 Nowadays I mostly dream about UXR.
I&amp;rsquo;m reachable at ismael@searchness.com 👋</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>💡 Searchness</title>
      <link>https://ismaelsow.com/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ismaelsow.com/software/</guid>
      <description>Searchness helps product teams record usability testing sessions and user interviews. It brings your recording, note-taking and insights generation under one roof and makes you more productive.
Available on desktop, iOS and Android.
Check it out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>